<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Critique Wheel Policies</title>
    <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Critique Wheel Policies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 21:42:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://policies.critiquewheel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Counseling and Prevention Resources</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/help-center/counseling-and-prevention-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 21:42:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/help-center/counseling-and-prevention-resources/</guid>
      <description>Counseling and Prevention Resources Here is a list of global helplines, because sometimes outside support is needed to help you make positive changes.
United States &amp;amp; Canada Crisis Text Line
https://www.crisistextline.org/ Text HOME to 741741 (USA &amp;amp; Canada)
Kids Help Phone (Canada)
https://kidshelpphone.ca/ Text CONNECT to 686868 (Canada) Call 1 800 668 6868 (Canada)
National Suicide Prevention Lifeline (USA)
http://www.suicidepreventionlifeline.org 1 800 273 TALK (8255) 1 800 SUICIDE (784 2433)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag a Story</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/faq/flag-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 09:59:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/faq/flag-story/</guid>
      <description>Flagging a Story or a Critique If you encounter a story that is incorrectly rated according to our guidelines, or any material which does not comply with our content guidelines, please report it using the flag icon button at one the page in question.
You will be presented with a choice of options.
Please choose the most relevant option to the issue you are having with the material. You may add additional information in the report details textbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copyright</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/faq/copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 17:58:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/faq/copyright/</guid>
      <description>Your Copyright: It Remains Yours. We&amp;rsquo;re working on making this more coherent.
But in brief, you retain all copyright on all stories you upload. Since this is a private, users only service, your story is not considered published by submitting it to the Critique Wheel for the purpose of getting critique.
You retain all original copyright on your work.
See terms and conditions for more information on intellectual property rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:57:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:17:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/content/</guid>
      <description>Content Guidelines Last Revised: August 31st, 2021
An Inclusive and Respectful Space At the Critique Wheel, we help writers improve their craft faster by exchanging critiques.
In order to create and maintain an inclusive and respectful space, we want our critiquers to know the kind of material they will find on the Critique Wheel and and what kind of material is not accepted.
Before you start using the Critique Wheel, please look at and read the following guidelines:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 13:54:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
Website Disclaimer The information provided by Critique Wheel (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”) on critiquewheel.blueseawriters.com (the “Site”) is for general informational purposes only. All information on the Site is provided in good faith, however we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability, or completeness of any information on the Site.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE SHALL WE HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF THE SITE OR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 12:51:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions Last Revised: August 31st, 2021
Introduction Welcome to Critique Wheel (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”)!
These Terms of Service (“Terms”, “Terms of Service”) govern your use of our website located at CritiqueWheel.BlueSeaWriters.com (together or individually “Service”) operated by Critique Wheel.
Our Privacy Policy also governs your use of our Service and explains how we collect, safeguard and disclose information that results from your use of our web pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 02:36:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
At Critique Wheel, accessible from https://critiquewheel.blueseawriters.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Critique Wheel and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in The Critique Wheel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
