<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Policies on Critique Wheel Policies</title>
    <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Policies on Critique Wheel Policies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:57:07 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:57:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:17:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/content/</guid>
      <description>Content Guidelines Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
Coming soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 13:54:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
Website Disclaimer The information provided by Critique Wheel (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”) on critiquewheel.blueseawriters.com (the “Site”) is for general informational purposes only. All information on the Site is provided in good faith, however we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability, or completeness of any information on the Site.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE SHALL WE HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF THE SITE OR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 12:51:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
Introduction Welcome to Critique Wheel (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”)!
These Terms of Service (“Terms”, “Terms of Service”) govern your use of our website located at CritiqueWheel.BlueSeaWriters.com (together or individually “Service”) operated by Critique Wheel.
Our Privacy Policy also governs your use of our Service and explains how we collect, safeguard and disclose information that results from your use of our web pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 02:36:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://policies.critiquewheel.com/policies/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Last Revised: May 1st, 2021
At Critique Wheel, accessible from https://critiquewheel.blueseawriters.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Critique Wheel and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in The Critique Wheel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
